Hi. In this lesson, we will focus on fixes and improvements.
So we will make a few improvements.
The first one, we have more data could sort of get to delete them.
We need to mention it, just to clean up our application.
And the next improvement is our application file really mess.
So we have IPI code, here's the utils to make the flock from currents, etc.
We're going to split it up, we're going to move APIs to APA folder, utils to utils folder.
We also, in our rate, we have an APA code, which is used under util, which is due to the conversion.
So it's not good. We need to split up the API, the get data, and the conversion itself, because it's util.
And it will be much easier to write the tests then.
And also, we need to do one fix, so it's how we dispose the result, because if I get the exchange rate,
I see it's correct, but when I start changing an amount, it's now it's wrong.
So because we update an amount, it's out the recalculation.
So what we do, we will just hide the result, we will use it to not click get exchange rates again.
And we also need to check that if user change the currency, or if he change the amount, or if he change currency from,
so we need to clean up it, and just hide it.
Okay, let's start with, this might be cleaning a mock data.
So as I mentioned, AI missed to remove this data, it's not good to keep them, because we use real API calls.
But now, and you'll clean up this key power project structure, clean, and up to date.
So I will ask AI to delete the specific file.
I of course can remove it by myself, but might be imported somewhere.
I can also ask AI, please remove all mocks, but sometimes he can make it wrong.
He can delete the wrong files, so you, the more the task to give him, the more context to give him.
So simple, I can write result, you will give, you will have.
So I will use agent, because I need to make some fixes.
So let's check, so he deleted currencies, he check that have been deleted, there are no direct imports to this file.
Okay, yeah, that's fine.
It was deleted and more imports.
So the next fix we will do, we will, we have to API calls with the cross one to get currencies,
with all supported currencies we have, and the next one, we have to get the latest controllers and rights.
It should be moved out from the details to the separate folder.
And same for this util, like the conversion util should be separate and stored on the utils folder,
and also this make from currency also should be separate one.
So because it's not, it's really a mess, so when we will write the unit test, we will need to do some refactoring,
we might have some difficulties.
So I prepared the prompt, so I will ask, move all API calls to source API folder in separate files,
and it mentions the name of the files like fetch currencies and get rates that he'll understand what exactly API calls I want to move.
I also mentioned that more conversion logic from data rates, this conversion logic, he did it here, yeah.
To separate util, like convert amount, which will be placed on the utils folder,
and also move helper function like make fleck from currency, which we use in app.tastic files,
the main application file also to use folder, also ask update all imports to match new paths.
So let's ask, and you'll see how he will do it.
Also, if you don't like the result, it might be because you use the model automatically,
and you can use the, I recommend you to use a cloud sonnet, so you can use sonnet or 0.5.
Nowadays, it's the latest model, it's really good for coding tasks for some research, so you can use it.
But because I'm on a free plan, I have limitations, so I will use auto.
You can also try to use the composer, it's something you presented from Kursor, which should be good for coding tasks.
So we'll see, okay, AI is finished, let's, it's a summary, it was smooth to get.
I'll open API folder, I see fetch currencies, yes, it looks okay, what is the abort signal?
Then all get rates, we also have, we get a URL problems, we set the URL, then we get the rates,
and then we return all the data, okay, it also looks fine, it's of course mode ideal,
because we duplicate the types right here, but it's fine for now, let's check the details we have,
convert amount, yes, it also looks good, yes, acceptable, I would say, and make like from currency, it also looks acceptable.
And now let's check our API f.t6, so yeah, we have f.t6, so we move the fetch in currencies,
here we use the fetch method, we also move this URL, okay, we also use get rates here,
to convert an amount, okay, we can click keep all, keep all the changes, it's now a bit better,
as we do rates, fetch rates, and it's separate utl, so we still have rates file, which is not used anymore, I suppose,
so let me check it here, so we don't use, and let's ask linear files, not all files, not used anymore,
when I say I mean this rates.ts file, let's see, we should identify it, yep, it was deleted, okay,
and now we're finished with doing these changes, we of course can do the refactoring, yes, because we can improve,
well, I just use the use effect, not react, but use effect, so we can do a lot of improvements here,
we can also ask to refactor this method, a lot of symbols, etc, so there are a lot of places to improve,
but then we spend a lot of time on just until slathons, so I won't do it, so last fix, I don't do,
I don't ask to fix how we will dispose the result, so because right now is displayed, always
and we need to dispose it only when we click get a change rates, and after we change any amount,
any currency, or we do the swap, so we just hide it, okay, I also prepared the prompt,
let's ask it, clear the result, display when the user changes, the amount of currencies,
all the result only after new conversion is completed, if no conversion yet,
keep the result there is empty, I'll show a short hand hint message, okay, all the prompts you can
find in specific words and with materials and prompts, so no worry you can codify them and run,
so let's see how we either do the task, so I think you should make it perfect,
okay, you know, use has converted, okay, if we have amount from up to was updated,
okay we first had the values state, okay, plus just check if it works, yeah, we need to run
application again, yeah, it works, so let me enter an amount and click on the word to see the result,
let me do it, we have the right, if I change, it works for the change of the amount, let's
change the currency, it works, let's change the currency to it works, what if you do the swap,
yep, it also works, okay, now let's show information with display, so, hey, this is page insulate,
straight, yeah, everything works perfect, or if you'd like to do any other improvements,
you can follow a approach with it, so you can ask to refactor it, to split some logic,
to, I don't know, improve some UI, add some new features, so you can play with it, I recommend
you to, I know, create an ideas, what else you can improve in this UI and try it by yourself,
might be to add, might be to add a history, what currencies we change might be, I don't know,
this way, some preferred currency, some might be anything else, okay, I'll see you in the next
last time, the value right, the unit test, I will show you how to do it, and how to ask the eye,
clearly to make it, with a good structure.